<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hugo-site on Khô Mực</title><link>/tags/hugo-site/</link><description>Recent content in hugo-site on Khô Mực</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/hugo-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A first post</title><link>/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</guid><description>Hi, I'm the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.
Here I am: content/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful.md To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}
My content section is: blog My layout is: single-series does this work? or this? Let&amp;rsquo;s start.
beginning middle end</description></item><item><title>A second post</title><link>/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</guid><description>Hi, I'm the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.
Here I am: content/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/index.md To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}
My content section is: blog My layout is: single-series Images in this page bundle: /blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/sidebar-inverse.jpg part 2! does this work? now for some very cool things more get ready!</description></item><item><title>A third post</title><link>/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</guid><description>Hi, I'm the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.
Here I am: content/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/index.markdown Here is my R Markdown source file: blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/index.Rmarkdown You'll want to edit this file, then re-knit to see the changes take effect in your site preview.
To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}
My content section is: blog My layout is: single-series Images in this page bundle: /blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/featured-photo.</description></item><item><title>Thảo Trang</title><link>/team/trang/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/team/trang/</guid><description>Chào bạn. 👋 Mình là Trang. Mình hiện tại đang làm khoa học dữ liệu ở công ty dược Bristol Myers Squibb.
Ngày xưa, vì là dân chuyên toán mình rất ngại viết văn, nhưng quá trình học cao học đã buộc mình phải viết (và sửa) rất nhiều. Vì thế, mình muốn chia sẻ kinh nghiệm mình đã thu thập được trong nhiều năm qua cho những bạn cùng hoàn cảnh với mình.</description></item><item><title>Hands for Hands</title><link>/team/hands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/team/hands/</guid><description>Hands For Hands Vietnam là nhóm hỗ trợ các em học sinh, sinh viên trong nhiều mảng khác nhau, bao gồm luyện thi IELTS, SAT, THPT. Với châm ngôn “Một bàn tay nắm một bàn tay&amp;quot;, dự án ên ưu tiên hàng đầu chất lượng giảng dạy và trải nghiệm của học viên, với lịch học theo sự sắp xếp của học sinh và giảng viên, lớp nhóm nhỏ dưới 7 bạn hoặc lớp 1-1.</description></item><item><title>A Spoonful of Hugo</title><link>/blog/spoonful-series/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/spoonful-series/</guid><description>** No content below YAML for the series _index. This file is a leaf bundle, and provides settings for the listing page layout and sidebar content.**</description></item><item><title>CSS Grid Scaffold</title><link>/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</guid><description>“Grid is the very first CSS module created specifically to solve the layout problems we&amp;rsquo;ve all been hacking our way around for as long as we&amp;rsquo;ve been making websites.” — Chris House, A Complete Guide to CSS Grid Layout 1
Overview Since I began building websites in Y2K, I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count how many times the phrase &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;there&amp;rsquo;s got to be a better way to do this&amp;rdquo; has passed my lips.</description></item><item><title>Built-in Contact Form</title><link>/blog/built-in-contact-form/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/built-in-contact-form/</guid><description>Formspree makes it easy to receive submissions from HTML forms on your static website. Functional Form This theme has a form-to-email feature built in, thanks to the simple Formspree integration. All you need to activate the form is a valid recipient email address saved in the front matter of the form (/content/forms/contact.md). Of course, the example shown below (your@email.here) must not be used.</description></item></channel></rss>